{
    "subject": "resource/Rambod_Javan",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Rambod Javan Tabrizi",
    "human_readable": "The full name of Rambod Javan is Rambod Javan Tabrizi.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.96518874168396,
            "question": "What is the full name of Rambod Javan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9259395003318787,
            "question": "What is Rambod Javan Tabrizi a reference to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9239729642868042,
            "question": "If someone called Rambod Javan 'Javan,' would they be using his full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8858550786972046,
            "question": "Is Rambod Javan's full name publicly available information?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8557589650154114,
            "question": "What is Rambod Javan's middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8543731570243835,
            "question": "How many parts are there to Rambod Javan's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8486831188201904,
            "question": "Does Rambod Javan have a middle name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8383818864822388,
            "question": "What is the last part of Rambod Javan's full name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05574158951640129,
            "question": "Can you provide examples of other people with multiple names?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.023159489035606384,
            "question": "What are some factors that might influence someone's choice to use a middle name?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The full name of Rambod Javan is Rambod Javan Tabrizi.",
            "html": "dbpedia_680_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide examples of other people with multiple names?",
            "html": "dbpedia_680_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the last part of Rambod Javan's full name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_680_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Rambod Javan have a middle name?",
            "html": "dbpedia_680_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_680_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_680_117.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_680_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_680_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_680_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_680_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_680_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_680_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_680_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_680_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents provide information that confirms Rambod Javan's full name as indeed being Rambod Javan Tabrizi."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Rambod Javan's full name, stating that he was \"born on 22 December 1971 in Shahrara\" and is also referred to as \"Rambod Javan Tabrizi\". Therefore, the triple \"The full name of Rambod Javan is Rambod Javan Tabrizi\" is supported by the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}